{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Schmitt",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Jacob_Taubes",
    "human_readable": "Carl Schmitt was influenced by Jacob Taubes.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9850243330001831,
            "question": "To what extent was Carl Schmitt influenced by Jacob Taubes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9554240703582764,
            "question": "Was Carl Schmitt familiar with the work of Jacob Taubes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9534315466880798,
            "question": "In what way did Jacob Taubes influence Carl Schmitt's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9417034983634949,
            "question": "What are some examples of Carl Schmitt's work that might have been influenced by Jacob Taubes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9367372989654541,
            "question": "Who influenced Carl Schmitt?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9104233384132385,
            "question": "How did Jacob Taubes contribute to Carl Schmitt's intellectual development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8354822993278503,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Carl Schmitt and Jacob Taubes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8058409094810486,
            "question": "Did Jacob Taubes' ideas shape Carl Schmitt's thinking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7985854744911194,
            "question": "Can you identify any common themes in the works of Carl Schmitt and Jacob Taubes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6911070942878723,
            "question": "What can we learn about Carl Schmitt by examining his influences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Schmitt was influenced by Jacob Taubes.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8615_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify any common themes in the works of Carl Schmitt and Jacob Taubes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8615_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Jacob Taubes' ideas shape Carl Schmitt's thinking?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8615_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Carl Schmitt and Jacob Taubes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8615_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8615_44.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Jacob Taubes was influenced by Carl Schmitt, not the other way around. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the documents, I found that:\n\n* There is no mention of Carl Schmitt being influenced by Jacob Taubes. Instead, it seems that both thinkers were influenced by each other's ideas, and Jacob Taubes even wrote a book called \"To Carl Schmitt: Letter and Reflections\" which critiques Schmitt's rigid social ordering.\n* Jacob Taubes was heavily influenced by Carl Schmitt, but there is no mention of the reverse.\n\nTherefore, the correct response is:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Jacob Taubes was influenced by figures such as Carl Schmitt, Max Weber, and Friedrich Nietzsche. There is no information suggesting that Carl Schmitt was influenced by Jacob Taubes. Therefore, the statement \"Carl Schmitt was influenced by Jacob Taubes\" is not supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text repeatedly emphasizes Taubes' profound influence on Schmitt, describing him as a central figure that \"literally wrote the book\" on political theology and highlighting their intellectual exchange through correspondence and lectures.  Furthermore, Taubes acknowledges Schmitt's reservations about liberal democracy while critiquing his rigid social ordering, indicating a dynamic where Taubes engages with and challenges Schmitt's ideas.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information explicitly states that Jacob Taubes was influenced by Carl Schmitt, not the other way around.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context clearly indicates that Jacob Taubes was influenced by Carl Schmitt, not the other way around. This influence is evident from statements like \"He [Taubes] was influenced by Carl Schmitt,\" and discussions of their shared engagement with political theology and history.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}